Welcome to the LNURL Testing Podcast.
This is a test episode for Lightning Network payment integration.
We'll be demonstrating value-for-value monetization using Lightning payments.
This episode includes multiple LNURL addresses for testing different Lightning wallets.
You can test payments to Alby, Strike, BTCPay, Zeus Cashu, and Primal.
We also have Lightning node pubkeys for keysend payments.
This feed is designed for podcast app developers and Lightning wallet developers.
Test your implementation with this known working feed structure.
The feed follows Podcast Index namespace standards for value blocks.
Thank you for testing Lightning Network podcast integration.
This concludes our LNURL testing episode.